<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='trafo.xsl' ?>
<articles>
	<article id='Tutorial'>
		Welcome to the Casie tutorial. Let's assume we have used two annotators to annotate the current text.
		Have a look at the words in boldface like <mark entity="Barack_Obama">Obama</mark> referring to the president of the United States of America. 
		When you move over it with your mouse cursor, you can see "Barack_Oba..." appearing twice. The first supplementary line corresponds to the first annotator and the second one to the second annotator.
		Both annotators got it right, so "Barack_Oba..." appears in green.
		But <mark entity="Michelle_Obama">Obama</mark> may also refer to <mark entity="Michelle_Obama"><mark entity="Barack_Obama">his</mark> wife</mark>.
		In this case the supplementary lines always appear, as at least one annotator has made a mistake.
		The first annotator got it wrong and the second hasn't found it at all, so both become marked in red.
		Move your mouse on top of a mention and a tooltip will give you details about it.
		Click on the third line of "<mark entity="Michelle_Obama">Michelle Obama</mark>" to mark all the spans annotated with <mark entity="Michelle_Obama">her</mark>.
		Click on a highlighted span or a span without a mention to go back to the normal mode.
	</article>
	<article id='Options'>
		Casie combines mentions if all of the activated annotators got it right. To show all annotations, disable the "conflicts" option.
		<br/>
		Click on "Show symbols" to display a &#x2714; or a &#x2718; at the end of the spans for correct or wrong annotations.
		When you want information about overlapping mentions, activate the "span limits" option.
		Parentheses mark the borders of the annotated spans, i.e. "(" indicates the start and ")" indicates the end.
	</article>
	<article id="Annotators">
		Deselect "annotator 2" to hide the second annotator. You can still click on mentions to highlight the corresponding chains. Casie recalculates which mentions to show in the split/compact view. You can also show the gold standard.
	</article>
	<article id='Evaluation'>
		Casie shows all available evaluation metrics in the drop-down list.
		Choose your preferred metric to see the computed precision and recall.
		Casie highlights the best annotator for recall and precision respectively.
	</article>
</articles>
